[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "state": "latinx",
    "question": "Are you Hispanic, LatinX, or Spanish?",
    "detail": "You may say yes to more than one",
    "answers": "LATINX"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "state": "race",
    "question": "What is your race?",
    "detail": "One or more categories may be selected",
    "multiple": true,
    "answers": "RACE"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "state": "gender",
    "question": "How do you describe yourself?",
    "answers": "GENDER"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "state": "sexual_orientation",
    "question": "Which of the following do you consider yourself to be?",
    "answers": "ORIENTATION"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "state": "living_situation",
    "question": "Describe where you live?",
    "answers": "HOUSING"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "state": "household_members",
    "question": "Who do you live with?",
    "detail": "Mark all that apply.",
    "multiple": true,
    "answers": "HOUSEHOLD"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "state": "suspension",
    "question": "Have you ever been suspended from school for drug or alcohol use?",
    "answers": "YES_NO"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "state": "arrested_in_last_month",
    "number_input": true,
    "question": "In the past 30 days, have you been arrested?"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "state": "informed_of_HIV_status",
    "question": "Have you ever been informed of your HIV status (this is, whether or not you are HIV-positive) based on the result of an HIV test?",
    "answers": "YES_NO"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "state": "informed_of_VH_status",
    "question": "Have you ever been informed of your viral hepatitis (VH) status (this is, whether or not you are infected with a hepitatis virus) based on the result of a VH test?",
    "answers": "YES_NO"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "state": "knowledge_of_healthcare_facility",
    "question": "Is there a doctor's office, health center, or other similar place that you usually go to when you are sick?",
    "answers": "YES_NO"
  }
]
